>> Jem Young: 谁能解释一下包是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Can anybody
explain what a packet is?
只要你拿着枪就好
Just take it take a shot at that.
你觉得包是什么
What do you think a packet is?
>> 扬声器 2: 信息的位。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A bit of information.
>> Jem Young: 没错，对。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly, right.
这是一点点的信息。
It's a little bit of information.
这是你能传输的最小的信息
It's the smallest bit of
information you can transmit.
严格来说，有一点是你能传递的最小的信息。
Well, technically a bit is the smallest
information you can transfer it.
但一个包就像一个信封
But a packet is,
think of it like an envelope.
包含数据的包络。
An envelope with data in it.
如果你想寄东西的话信封上有什么
And what does an envelope have on it,
if you're trying to mail something?
它有一个关于你要去哪儿的地址
It's got an address about
where you're trying to get to.
它得到了关于你从哪里来的信息
It's got information about
where you're coming from,
以防它要回来的时候
just in case and when it has to come back.
在这个包里有信息
And inside that packet
has the information.
这就是包的内容。
And that's what a packet is.
它只是这一基本单元的信息，说明一切都是如何传输的。
It's just this base unit of information
of how everything's transmitting.
事实，我在互联网上跟你说话的方式只是几十亿，万亿，
Fact, the way I'm talking to you on the
internet is just billions, and trillions,
数万亿的信息包正在移动
and trillions of packets
are moving right now.
但包主要包含元数据。
But a packet mainly contains metadata.
人们认为它主要是数据，就像你邮寄一个信封，你在想，
People think it's mainly data, like when
you mail an envelope you're thinking,
我希望有人能收到我的信或者我从网上买的东西
I sure hope someone gets my letter or
this thing I bought off the internet.
但是真正的信息包是什么，关键信息是什么，在哪里，
But really what the packet is, what the
the key information is, where it's going,
它是从哪里来的，然后所有这些元数据都附加到它。
where it came from, and
then all these metadata attached to it.
因此，元数据通常为标题形式。
So that metadata is usually
in the form of headers.
但这个包又不是
But again, the packet is it's not
就像我在网上传的这些视频包一样
just like these video packets I'm
sending out over the internet right now.
这不只是一个包
It's not just one packet.
它是它们的数万亿，并且通常使用 TCP。
It's trillions of them and
often using TCP.
它从一个开始说，嘿，我有一个。
It starts with one and
it says like, hey, I've got one.
还有 50 个我的表妹们也来了
And there's 50 more of my
cousins coming along too.
然后当他们点击服务器时，它会把它们都放在一个校验和中。
And then when they hit the server,
it puts them all together in a checksum.
这就是为什么 TCP 被称为纠错的原因
And that's why TCP is called
error correcting because it has
所有这些信息包都说，嘿，有 50 个包。
all these packets, and it says like,
hey, there's 50 packets.
客户说，嘿，除了两个人我都拿到了
And the client says, hey,
I got all of them except for two.
我少了 49 和 37
I'm missing 49 and 37.
这会把它反馈给服务器，服务器上说，我承认。
And that sends it back to the server and
the server says, I acknowledge that.
让我发最后两包吧
Let me send those last two packets.
这就是为什么因为你保证能拿到这个
That's why it's called error correcting
because you're guaranteed to get this
每单个时间都有包。
packet every single time.
发送刚广播数据的 UDP 包的 Versus UDP 。
Versus UDP which sends UDP packets
which are just broadcasting data.
如果你能拿到剩下的信息就无所谓了
It doesn't matter if you get
the rest of the packets.
最终他们会来的
Eventually they'l come through.
因为它不出错。
Because it doesn't error correct.
这就是为什么 TCP 更快的原因。
That's why TCP is faster.